Most habit apps ask what you want to do.
This one asks who you want to become.
It's a two-minute chat with an AI coach.
You tell it your goal — mine was running my first 5K.
And it writes you a real plan.
Milestones, and a few small daily actions.
Each day, you check off a couple of small things.
Finish the day, and it says so.
Your progress fills in — and never resets.
Shape it your way: milestones, dates, how often.
Every week, your coach checks in,
and remembers what you did.
Then it actually coaches you —
adjusting the plan so you don't burn out.
Specific, personal, every single week.
Not a tracker. Someone in your corner.
Resolution Companion — free on the App Store.